{
    "Questions": [
        {
            "qId": 1,
            "question": "What hotel did we stay at during New Year?",
            "answer": "toronto don valley",
            "link": "S7O22T3tf5A"
        },
        {
            "qId": 2,
            "question": "How many lines on Lazeez makes you a chad? (write numbers as words and end with lines)",
            "answer": "five lines",
            "link": "vErAVnOv-6g"
        },
        {
            "qId": 3,
            "question": "What abomination did you drink based on drub and tanmays suggestions?",
            "answer": "matcha frappe",
            "link": "0B0kSGrXNVY"
        },
        {
            "qId": 4,
            "question": "Where did we have dinner on the cold wintery night of New Year’s Eve? (write it all as one word)",
            "answer": "myrotimydosa",
            "link": "s7uJaJ4TBIU"
        },
        {
            "qId": 5,
            "question": "Where did you go on your first date?",
            "answer": "columbia park",
            "link": "NisLIEzhFSU"
        },
        {
            "qId": 6,
            "question": "What is the pokemon mascot of Ottawa Trip?",
            "answer": "dragonite",
            "link": "YEDnzsX15eQ"
        },
        {
            "qId": 7,
            "question": "What sport did we play the night before ECE124 midterm",
            "answer": "cricket",
            "link": "RDcOoB4rCdI"
        },
        {
            "qId": 8,
            "question": "What are we buying after graduation?",
            "answer": "panda",
            "link": "m9IRVCHXv0Y"
        },
        {
            "qId": 9,
            "question": "What’s Vaishnavi’s brain capacity? (spell numbers in words)",
            "answer": "five percent",
            "link": "onVcIoqATBc"
        },
        {
            "qId": 10,
            "question": "What’s the first name of the driver that made you drink for the first time",
            "answer": "max",
            "link": "LG1DBC_PBuw"
        },
        {
            "qId": 11,
            "question": "What do we fuck?",
            "answer": "the clouds",
            "link": "9IVO5Dsz1KI"
        }
    ]
}